[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "CD", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 50, "question": "Judge Mukasey, what is the legal position with this man as we stand today?", "question_tokens": ["Judge", "Mukasey", ",", "what", "is", "the", "legal", "position", "with", "this", "man", "as", "we", "stand", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 51, "answer": "Well, if in fact he had anything to do with the bombing of 103, that is either by way of transmitting the order or giving the orders, then he could be tried by a Scottish court.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "if", "in", "fact", "he", "had", "anything", "to", "do", "with", "the", "bombing", "of", "103", ",", "that", "is", "either", "by", "way", "of", "transmitting", "the", "order", "or", "giving", "the", "orders", ",", "then", "he", "could", "be", "tried", "by", "a", "Scottish", "court", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Judge Mukasey"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "Will they be given that chance, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Will", "they", "be", "given", "that", "chance", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "I think they'll be given the chance to talk to him.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "they", "'ll", "be", "given", "the", "chance", "to", "talk", "to", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gadhafi"]}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "What do you make of what is happening in Libya right now just -- as an American and as a judge?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "what", "is", "happening", "in", "Libya", "right", "now", "just", "--", "as", "an", "American", "and", "as", "a", "judge", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "RB", ":", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "As an American, obviously to the extent that somebody has it in mind to get rid of Gadhafi, that's all to the good.", "answer_tokens": ["As", "an", "American", ",", "obviously", "to", "the", "extent", "that", "somebody", "has", "it", "in", "mind", "to", "get", "rid", "of", "Gadhafi", ",", "that", "'s", "all", "to", "the", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Libya"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Moussa Koussa"]}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "MD", "VB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 96, "question": "Would you ever see a position where you would trade immunity for people like Moussa Koussa in return for the capture of Gadhafi himself?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "ever", "see", "a", "position", "where", "you", "would", "trade", "immunity", "for", "people", "like", "Moussa", "Koussa", "in", "return", "for", "the", "capture", "of", "Gadhafi", "himself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 97, "answer": "Well, Moussa Koussa should be given a really cushy cell somewhere, and I understand that he needs medical treatment, and that would be great, as well.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Moussa", "Koussa", "should", "be", "given", "a", "really", "cushy", "cell", "somewhere", ",", "and", "I", "understand", "that", "he", "needs", "medical", "treatment", ",", "and", "that", "would", "be", "great", ",", "as", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Moussa Koussa", "Gadhafi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Kuwait"]}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "What was that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "What you had in Kuwait was the resignation of the government.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "you", "had", "in", "Kuwait", "was", "the", "resignation", "of", "the", "government", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 131, "question": "Do you predict economic turmoil for quite -- some considerable time?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "predict", "economic", "turmoil", "for", "quite", "--", "some", "considerable", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "RB", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 132, "answer": "I predict uncertainty for quite a bit of time.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "predict", "uncertainty", "for", "quite", "a", "bit", "of", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "LOCATION": ["Tokyo"]}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNP", "NN", ",", "CC", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "And what did you find?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "did", "you", "find", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "So I went there just to thank our colleagues who have been doing an amazing job in our Tokyo office, and nothing, Piers, prepared me.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "I", "went", "there", "just", "to", "thank", "our", "colleagues", "who", "have", "been", "doing", "an", "amazing", "job", "in", "our", "Tokyo", "office", ",", "and", "nothing", ",", "Piers", ",", "prepared", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 160, "question": "Or in terms of economy, are they able to withstand it on their own?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "in", "terms", "of", "economy", ",", "are", "they", "able", "to", "withstand", "it", "on", "their", "own", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "So in the short term, this is a headwind for everybody, because it disrupts demand, it disrupts supply chains.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "in", "the", "short", "term", ",", "this", "is", "a", "headwind", "for", "everybody", ",", "because", "it", "disrupts", "demand", ",", "it", "disrupts", "supply", "chains", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "Is your general advice to the American consumer tighten the belt a bit?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "your", "general", "advice", "to", "the", "American", "consumer", "tighten", "the", "belt", "a", "bit", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "It is.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "Going to be a bumpy ride?", "question_tokens": ["Going", "to", "be", "a", "bumpy", "ride", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "It's going to be a bumpy ride.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "a", "bumpy", "ride", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 173, "question": "If there's one thing you need to know about my next guest is don't bet against Dwayne Johnson, the man you may known as \"The Rock,\" is a star in the ring, a star in Hollywood, a star -- just about a star everything, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["If", "there", "'s", "one", "thing", "you", "need", "to", "know", "about", "my", "next", "guest", "is", "do", "n't", "bet", "against", "Dwayne", "Johnson", ",", "the", "man", "you", "may", "known", "as", "``", "The", "Rock", ",", "''", "is", "a", "star", "in", "the", "ring", ",", "a", "star", "in", "Hollywood", ",", "a", "star", "--", "just", "about", "a", "star", "everything", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "EX", "VBZ", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", ":", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "A star everything, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "star", "everything", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dwayne Johnson"], "LOCATION": ["Hollywood"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "RP", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 178, "question": "What do you think that has come from?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "that", "has", "come", "from", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 179, "answer": "I would have to say -- I would have to say growing up and the examples that were set for me from my parents.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "have", "to", "say", "--", "I", "would", "have", "to", "say", "growing", "up", "and", "the", "examples", "that", "were", "set", "for", "me", "from", "my", "parents", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 194, "question": "Did you ever imagine you'd reach the stage where you're a $10 million-a-movie star?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "ever", "imagine", "you", "'d", "reach", "the", "stage", "where", "you", "'re", "a", "$", "10", "million-a-movie", "star", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "$", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 195, "answer": "No, I didn't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$10 million-a-movie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "And you say that's mainly from your parents, you think?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "say", "that", "'s", "mainly", "from", "your", "parents", ",", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "OHNSON: Well, I think a good portion it is, sure.", "answer_tokens": ["OHNSON", ":", "Well", ",", "I", "think", "a", "good", "portion", "it", "is", ",", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "Mr. President, are you OK?", "question_tokens": ["Mr.", "President", ",", "are", "you", "OK", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "Oh, my god.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "my", "god", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. President"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Hawaii", "Hawaii"]}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", ":", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "JJ", ",", "CC", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "NNP", ":", "NNP", "POS", "DT", "RB", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "When you look at what's happened with Barack Obama, do you see parallels with your life?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "look", "at", "what", "'s", "happened", "with", "Barack", "Obama", ",", "do", "you", "see", "parallels", "with", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "Well, the -- certainly the ones that you just mentioned, sure, and plus I think, you know, growing up in Hawaii -- Hawaii's a very warm and proud place to grow up.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "--", "certainly", "the", "ones", "that", "you", "just", "mentioned", ",", "sure", ",", "and", "plus", "I", "think", ",", "you", "know", ",", "growing", "up", "in", "Hawaii", "--", "Hawaii", "'s", "a", "very", "warm", "and", "proud", "place", "to", "grow", "up", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 270, "question": "Have you met him?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "met", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 271, "answer": "I've talked to the phone with him.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "talked", "to", "the", "phone", "with", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 275, "question": "What was that about?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "that", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 276, "answer": "Oh, many private things, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "many", "private", "things", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 277, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 278, "answer": "No, not at all.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "You ever think maybe I'll have a go?", "question_tokens": ["You", "ever", "think", "maybe", "I", "'ll", "have", "a", "go", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "Sure -- you know, I thought about it.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "--", "you", "know", ",", "I", "thought", "about", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["United States of America"]}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "Well, in what way?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "in", "what", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "WP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "Ultimate power, you're the president of the United States of America.", "answer_tokens": ["Ultimate", "power", ",", "you", "'re", "the", "president", "of", "the", "United", "States", "of", "America", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "What are the things that would really be passionate to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "the", "things", "that", "would", "really", "be", "passionate", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "I would be passionate about taking care of our troops and protecting our troops.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "be", "passionate", "about", "taking", "care", "of", "our", "troops", "and", "protecting", "our", "troops", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "Has anyone said that before?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "anyone", "said", "that", "before", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "VBN", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "They have.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "have", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 328, "question": "How do you think -- how do you think he's doing?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "think", "--", "how", "do", "you", "think", "he", "'s", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 329, "answer": "I think he's doing a great job, and I'm very, very proud of him.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "'s", "doing", "a", "great", "job", ",", "and", "I", "'m", "very", ",", "very", "proud", "of", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "But everyone is asking one question, are you ever going to get back and start wrestling again?", "question_tokens": ["But", "everyone", "is", "asking", "one", "question", ",", "are", "you", "ever", "going", "to", "get", "back", "and", "start", "wrestling", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "CD", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "CC", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "I'm open to it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "open", "to", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 361, "question": "You are?", "question_tokens": ["You", "are", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 362, "answer": "Very open to it.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "open", "to", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "You still work together, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "still", "work", "together", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "We do.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "VB", "WP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "What was your expectation of marriage?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "expectation", "of", "marriage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "My expectation -- my expectation of marriage, you know, I don't quite know what my expectation of marriage was back then.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "expectation", "--", "my", "expectation", "of", "marriage", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "quite", "know", "what", "my", "expectation", "of", "marriage", "was", "back", "then", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 403, "question": "Who's the lucky girl in your life now then?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "'s", "the", "lucky", "girl", "in", "your", "life", "now", "then", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 404, "answer": "I can't tell you that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "ca", "n't", "tell", "you", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", ":", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", ":", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "JJ", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 415, "question": "How have you managed to achieve that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "have", "you", "managed", "to", "achieve", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 416, "answer": "Well, privacy's important to me and it's important -- you know, my relationships -- the relationships I have, whether it -- regardless of who it is, whether it's my girlfriend, ex-wife's little girl friends, whatever it is, it -- it's always been important to me to be private and live privately.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "privacy", "'s", "important", "to", "me", "and", "it", "'s", "important", "--", "you", "know", ",", "my", "relationships", "--", "the", "relationships", "I", "have", ",", "whether", "it", "--", "regardless", "of", "who", "it", "is", ",", "whether", "it", "'s", "my", "girlfriend", ",", "ex-wife", "'s", "little", "girl", "friends", ",", "whatever", "it", "is", ",", "it", "--", "it", "'s", "always", "been", "important", "to", "me", "to", "be", "private", "and", "live", "privately", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "Or has it put you off for life going through a bad divorce?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "has", "it", "put", "you", "off", "for", "life", "going", "through", "a", "bad", "divorce", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "No, not at all.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 436, "question": "You know that, you know?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "that", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 437, "answer": "Of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "TO", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "-- was genius, wasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["--", "was", "genius", ",", "was", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "Well, to say -- it was genius.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "to", "say", "--", "it", "was", "genius", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "Is all this really necessary to apprehend two men?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "all", "this", "really", "necessary", "to", "apprehend", "two", "men", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "One's a former federal officer, spent five years in deep cover.", "answer_tokens": ["One", "'s", "a", "former", "federal", "officer", ",", "spent", "five", "years", "in", "deep", "cover", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "Can you remember them?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "remember", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJR", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "What were they?", "question_tokens": ["What", "were", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "Has he told you that he loves you now?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "he", "told", "you", "that", "he", "loves", "you", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "He has, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "has", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "What else would you put in there?", "question_tokens": ["What", "else", "would", "you", "put", "in", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "Being a good dad is one.", "answer_tokens": ["Being", "a", "good", "dad", "is", "one", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "Like to win an Oscar?", "question_tokens": ["Like", "to", "win", "an", "Oscar", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "I would love to, sure.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "love", "to", ",", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 551, "question": "Practiced your speech?", "question_tokens": ["Practiced", "your", "speech", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 552, "answer": "Sure, I would love to.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", ",", "I", "would", "love", "to", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 561, "question": "Who's the one person you believe -- if you had to choose one -- you owe most to?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "'s", "the", "one", "person", "you", "believe", "--", "if", "you", "had", "to", "choose", "one", "--", "you", "owe", "most", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "CD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 562, "answer": "My mom.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "mom", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers Morgan"]}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 629, "question": "If I was to ask you, Jerry Weintraub is -- what would you say?", "question_tokens": ["If", "I", "was", "to", "ask", "you", ",", "Jerry", "Weintraub", "is", "--", "what", "would", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", ":", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 630, "answer": "I'm on Piers Morgan today.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "on", "Piers", "Morgan", "today", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jerry Weintraub"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 631, "question": "But how would you describe yourself?", "question_tokens": ["But", "how", "would", "you", "describe", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 632, "answer": "You know, it's hard for me to describe myself.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "hard", "for", "me", "to", "describe", "myself", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 648, "question": "What was he like -- Sinatra?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "he", "like", "--", "Sinatra", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", ":", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 649, "answer": "He was a great guy.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "was", "a", "great", "guy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sinatra"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sinatra"]}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "RB", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 683, "question": "What do you think separates the good from the great when it comes to stars?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "separates", "the", "good", "from", "the", "great", "when", "it", "comes", "to", "stars", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 684, "answer": "I think they're -- well, Sinatra knew how to tell a story in song.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "they", "'re", "--", "well", ",", "Sinatra", "knew", "how", "to", "tell", "a", "story", "in", "song", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 688, "question": "Is it the same thing?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "the", "same", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 689, "answer": "Sure, it is.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", ",", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 698, "question": "You sad to see her go?", "question_tokens": ["You", "sad", "to", "see", "her", "go", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 699, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 716, "question": "And who's the woman?", "question_tokens": ["And", "who", "'s", "the", "woman", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 717, "answer": "The women love him.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "women", "love", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Angelina Jolie"], "PERSON": ["Angie"]}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "NNP", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 718, "question": "Who's the woman?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "'s", "the", "woman", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 719, "answer": "I think right now of all the ladies, depending on the kind of role it is, Angie -- Angelina Jolie is brilliant.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "right", "now", "of", "all", "the", "ladies", ",", "depending", "on", "the", "kind", "of", "role", "it", "is", ",", "Angie", "--", "Angelina", "Jolie", "is", "brilliant", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Smith"]}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 734, "question": "And who would you pick to play you in a movie?", "question_tokens": ["And", "who", "would", "you", "pick", "to", "play", "you", "in", "a", "movie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 735, "answer": "Will Smith.", "answer_tokens": ["Will", "Smith", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 744, "question": "How have you pulled this off, Jerry?", "question_tokens": ["How", "have", "you", "pulled", "this", "off", ",", "Jerry", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 745, "answer": "Well, I haven't pulled it off.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "have", "n't", "pulled", "it", "off", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jerry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 790, "question": "Well, you picked very good women, haven't you?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "picked", "very", "good", "women", ",", "have", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 791, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110331pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 792, "question": "That's the trick, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "the", "trick", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 793, "answer": "I've been lucky twice.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "been", "lucky", "twice", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]